{
    "id": "c0693495348c4b23bce5da7ad7bf7d8d",
    "title": "Synonyms worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "83ae83c791e849deaacc3573e38832f5",
            "title": "Synonyms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The committee was not 'disposed' to hold another meeting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "inclined",
                        "disorganized",
                        "annoyed",
                        "excited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The special TV report 'disrupted' regular programming.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "satisfied",
                        "complemented",
                        "interrupted",
                        "continued"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He 'dissipated' his inheritance in less than six months.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "accumulated",
                        "wasted",
                        "saved",
                        "hoarded"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If enough members 'dissent', the new bill won’t be approved.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "agree",
                        "disagree",
                        "support",
                        "question"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A thunderstorm came up and 'dispersed' the picnickers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "gathered",
                        "scattered",
                        "summoned",
                        "organized"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy’s recklessness 'dismayed' his mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "impressed",
                        "distressed",
                        "pleased",
                        "annoyed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The 'disguised' commandos slipped through the enemy’s defense.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "camouflaged",
                        "skilled",
                        "trained",
                        "experienced"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Laws have been passed against religious 'discrimination'.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tolerance",
                        "intolerance",
                        "bias",
                        "fanaticism"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog luckily 'disgorged' the bone from his throat.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expelled",
                        "swallowed",
                        "choked",
                        "gulped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The plane would probably 'disintegrate' at that high speed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fuse",
                        "crumble",
                        "merge",
                        "stop"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}